Farah reporting
I'd be watching your back out there
furry huh then I have nothing to worry
about
I always dreamed of the day we would
fight together wanting a better life for
you with all I ever dreamed of
mom I know why you didn't want me to
join overwatch but it's still what I
want I didn't want that life for you but
I know that it's your decision
and I will support it
mccrane where did you learn to shoot
like that was it jack
Gabriel always was a good shot but I got
a few pointers from the best that'd be
your mother
keep the skies clear for me let's keep
the skies clear together Faja your
mother always hoped you'd follow in her
footsteps she did funny she never
mentioned that to me
Farah if your mother could see you now I
think she'd be proud of you there's a
first time for everything I guess see
you in the air
your mother would have been proud of you
he didn't know my mother very well then
Reinhardt you know I had a poster of you
on my wall when I was younger I remember
the poster my hair was amazing
Reinhardt are we still on for ice
fishing you're not still sore about last
year are you I'll show you I'll catch
twice as many as you this year
hater bein check out my new suit mark
six state-of-the-art job Church
concussion rockets yes it's looking
pretty good
hey Torbjorn what do you think of my new
suit job Church concussion rockets yes
it's looking pretty good
hey Toby on check out this new wrapped
Orion prototype ever seen anything like
it
job search concussion rockets yes it's
looking pretty good
you're so lucky tracer ever since I was
a little girl I dreamed of joining
overwatch maybe you'll still get your
chance who knows what the future holds
Farra your mother was a hero to me to
all of us you probably knew her better
than me
oh sorry Reinhardt
got you this time Jesse
don't mess with my family
mum you're amazing
Reinhart you still got it
you show him Reinhart